{
  "english": [
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Elephant",
      "right-answer": "elefant",
      "wrong-answer": ["lejon", "krokodil", "antilop"],
      "category": "animals"
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Tiger",
      "right-answer": "tiger",
      "wrong-answer": [ "björn", "hund", "katt"],
      "category": "animals" 
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Giraffe",
      "right-answer": "giraff",
      "wrong-answer": ["noshörning", "elefant", "apa"],
      "category": "animals"
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Monkey",
      "right-answer": "apa",
      "wrong-answer": ["elefant", "katt", "fågel"],
      "category": "animals" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Lion", 
      "right-answer": "lejon",
      "wrong-answer": [ "tiger", "elefant", "häst"],
      "category": "animals" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Zebra", 
      "right-answer": "zebra", 
      "wrong-answer": ["giraff", "elefant", "ko"],
      "category": "animals" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Dolphin",
      "right-answer": "delfin",
      "wrong-answer": [ "val", "haj", "fisk"],
      "category": "animals" 
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Penguin",
      "right-answer": "pingvin",
      "wrong-answer": ["elefant", "papegoja", "fågel"],
      "category": "animals"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Kangaroo",
      "right-answer": "känguru",
      "wrong-answer": [ "koala", "elefant", "lejon"],
      "category": "animals"
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Eagle",
      "right-answer": "örn", 
      "wrong-answer": ["falk", "fladdermus", "fisk"],
      "category": "animals" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Blue", 
      "right-answer": "blå", 
      "wrong-answer": ["gul", "röd", "grön"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Green", 
      "right-answer": "grön", 
      "wrong-answer": ["blå", "rosa", "svart"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Red",
      "right-answer": "röd", 
      "wrong-answer": ["gul", "blå", "lila"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Yellow",
      "right-answer": "gul", 
      "wrong-answer": ["blå", "röd", "vit"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Purple",
      "right-answer": "lila",
      "wrong-answer": ["orange", "grön", "rosa"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Orange", 
      "right-answer": "orange", 
      "wrong-answer": ["röd", "gul", "brun"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Pink", 
      "right-answer":"rosa", 
      "wrong-answer": ["lila", "blå", "grön"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Brown", 
      "right-answer": "brun", 
      "wrong-answer": ["grön", "röd", "gul"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Black", 
      "right-answer": "svart", 
      "wrong-answer": ["vit", "blå", "grå"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "White", 
      "right-answer": "vit", 
      "wrong-answer": ["svart", "brun", "grön"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Football",
      "right-answer": "fotboll", 
      "wrong-answer": ["hockey", "basket", "tennis"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Basketball",
      "right-answer": "basket", 
      "wrong-answer": ["fotboll", "simning", "golf"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Tennis",
      "right-answer": "tennis", 
      "wrong-answer": ["fotboll", "bordtennis", "volleyboll"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Swimming",
      "right-answer": "simning", 
      "wrong-answer": ["löpning", "cykling", "basket"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Running",
      "right-answer": "löpning", 
      "wrong-answer": ["simning", "cykling", "basket"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Cycling",
      "right-answer": "cykling",
      "wrong-answer": ["simning", "löpning", "fotboll"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Volleyball",
      "right-answer": "volleyboll", 
      "wrong-answer": ["fotboll", "basket", "tennis"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Golf", 
      "right-answer": "golf", 
      "wrong-answer": ["tennis", "fotboll", "basket"],
      "category": "sports" 
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Hockey",
      "right-answer": "ishockey", 
      "wrong-answer": ["fotboll", "basket", "tennis"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Skiing",
      "right-answer": "skidåkning", 
      "wrong-answer": ["simning", "löpning", "cykling"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Doctor",
      "right-answer": "läkare", 
      "wrong-answer": ["lärare", "kock", "servitör"],
      "category": "occupations"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Teacher",
      "right-answer": "lärare", 
      "wrong-answer": ["läkare", "servitör", "kock"],
      "category": "occupations"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Engineer",
      "right-answer": "ingenjör", 
      "wrong-answer": ["läkare", "advokat", "tandläkare"],
      "category": "occupations"
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Chef", 
      "right-answer": "kock", 
      "wrong-answer": ["läkare", "servitör", "lärare"],
      "category": "occupations" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Pilot", 
      "right-answer": "pilot", 
      "wrong-answer": ["läkare", "brandman", "polis"],
      "category": "occupations" 
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Lawyer",
      "right-answer": "advokat", 
      "wrong-answer": ["läkare", "ingenjör", "tandläkare"],
      "category": "occupations"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Nurse",
      "right-answer": "sjuksköterska", 
      "wrong-answer": ["läkare", "lärare", "kock"],
      "category": "occupations"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Artist",
      "right-answer": "konstnär", 
      "wrong-answer": ["läkare", "ingenjör", "advokat"],
      "category": "occupations"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Firefighter",
      "right-answer": "brandman",
      "wrong-answer": ["pilot", "läkare", "polis"],
      "category": "occupations"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Police officer",
      "right-answer": "polis",
      "wrong-answer": ["läkare", "kock", "servitör"],
      "category": "occupations"
    }
  ]
}
